Guide to the New York University Archives Collection on Commencement Celebrations Webpages MC.354
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection on Commencement Celebrations Webpages
May 2020-ongoing
New York University Archives
New York University
New York University. Gallatin Division
New York University. College of Arts and Science
New York University. School of Law
New York University. Tandon School of Engineering
Leonard N. Stern School of Business
New York University. Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service.
New York University. School of Global Public Health
Steinhardt School of Education
New York University. College of Nursing
New York University in Abu Dhabi
New York University. College of Dentistry
New York University in Shanghai
New York University. School of Social Work
New York University. Graduate School of Arts and Science
New York University. School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions
Tisch School of the Arts
MC.354
201 websites in 201 archived websites.
New York University Archives Collection on Commencement Celebrations Webpages documents the commencement proceedings for New York University and its school ceremonies. The collection was established in response to the COVID-19 pandemic. The collection contains video streams of the ceremonies, awards, student profiles, messages from deans, names of graduates, and commencement programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please contact the Archives with specific questions regarding access to such records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Websites were selected by Janet Bunde and Nicole Greenhouse and captured through the use of Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. The accession numbers associated with these websites are 2020.039, 2020.042, 2021.004, 2021.005, 2021.007, 2021.052, 2021.067, 2022.001, 2022.002, 2022.003, 2022.053, 2022.060, 2022.062, 2022.083, 2023.036, 2024.057, and 2024.060.
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the special.collections@nyu.edu.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by record group.
Historical Note
In March 2020, New York University shifted to remote activities due to the COVID-19 pandemic. This led to the postponement of in-person commencement events and a pivot to virtual events in May 2020. The COVID-19 pandemic continued into 2021, and virtual commencement ceremonies also occurred that year. In 2022, the university went back to in-person commencement ceremonies and the university and schools also celebrated the Classes of 2020 and 2021 also in-person that year. Commencement ceremonies have continued in-person since 2022 every May. Each school holds its own ceremonies in addition to an All-University commencement held at Yankee Stadium.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
Scope and Contents
New York University Archives Collection on Virtual Commencement Celebrations Webpages (2020-ongoing) documents the virtual commencement proceedings for New York University and its school ceremonies from 2020-2022 as well as in-person ceremonies that were held from 2022 onwards. The collection contains video streams of the ceremonies, videos of speeches and performances at the ceremonies, awards, student profiles, messages from deans, names of graduates, frequently asked questions, photographs of graduating students, and commencement programs. The collection also includes all university commencement proceedings. The collection also includes information on cultural and identity-based ceremonies.
Appraisal
Websites were rescoped to attempt to capture videos embedded in the website. Embedded Youtube and Vimeo video files on the site were captured, but do not render in the archived copy. Future changes to the Wayback Machine may allow the files to be played.
Marching Order websites were captured but cannot be played back.
Accruals
Annual accruals are expected.
Commencement ceremonies; Video recordings.; COVID-19 (Disease); Commencement ceremonies -- 21st century.
- Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events/University Events (RG 7.4), May 2020-ongoing
  - 2020/2021 Full Commencement Ceremony Video, August 2022
  - 2020/2021 Commencement Preshow Video, September 2022
  - 2022 Full Commencement Ceremony Video, August 2022
  - 2023 Ceremony Video, June-July 2023
  - 2022 Commencement Preshow Video, September 2022
  - 2023 NYU Commencement (Full Ceremony), June 2023
  - All-University Commencement, May 2020-ongoing
  - All-University Commencement, June 2022-ongoing
  - All-University Commencement 2020/2021 Ceremony Video, June-July 2022
  - All-University Commencement 2021 Virtual Ceremony, May-June 2021
  - All-University Commencement 2022 Ceremony Video, June-July 2022
  - All-University Commencement 2024: Full Program, June 2024
  - All-University Commencement Frequently Asked Questions, May 2020-ongoing
  - All-University Commencement Student Profiles, May 2020-May 2021
  - Class of 2021 Memories, May-June 2021
  - Cultural and Identity-based Graduations, June 2022-ongoing
  - Events and Celebrations, June 2022-ongoing
  - Grad Alley, May 2020
  - Graduation Events, May-June 2021
  - Information for Graduates, May-June 2021
  - School Ceremonies, May 2020-ongoing
- Office of Student Affairs, LGBTQ+ Student Center (RG 12.15), May-June 2021
  - Lavender Graduation Celebration 2021, May-June 2021
- College of Arts and Science (RG 19), May 2020-ongoing
  - College of Arts and Science 2021 Virtual Celebration Video, January 2022
  - College of Arts and Science Baccalaureate, July 2022
  - College of Arts and Science Baccalaureate Livestream, May-June 2020
  - College of Arts and Science Baccalaureate Video, June-September 2023
  - College of Arts and Science Past Ceremonies, June 2023-ongoing
  - College of Arts and Science Senior Class, May 2020-June 2022
  - College of Arts and Science Senior Class, June 2023-ongoing
- Graduate School of Arts and Science (RG 20), May 2020-ongoing
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science 2024 Convocation Program, June 2024
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Convocation, May 2020
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Convocation, May-July 2021
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Convocation, June-July 2022
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Convocation, June 2023-ongoing
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Convocation Frequently Asked Questions, June 2024
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Degree Recipients, June 2024
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Doctoral & M.S. Convocation, June 2023-ongoing
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Doctoral & Psychology M.A. Ceremony, June 2024
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Doctoral Convocation Video, July 2023
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Master's Convocation, June 2023-ongoing
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Master's Convocation Ceremony, June 2024
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Master's Convocation Video, July 2023
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Past Ceremonies, June 2024
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Virtual Celebration Video, May-July 2021
- Liberal Studies Program (RG 21.47), June 2020-ongoing
  - Global Liberal Studies Baccalaureate Ceremony for the Class of 2022, June 2022
  - Global Liberal Studies Baccalaureate Ceremony for the Class of 2023, June 2023
  - Global Liberal Studies Baccalaureate Ceremony for the Class of 2024, June 2024
  - Global Liberal Studies Graduation, June 2022-ongoing
  - Global Liberal Studies Graduation Celebration for the Class of 2020, June 2020
  - Global Liberal Studies Graduation Celebration for the Class of 2021, May 2021
  - Global Liberal Studies Toast to the Class of 2021, May-June 2021
  - Liberal Studies Marching Order, June 2020
  - Liberal Studies Marching Order, June 2020
  - Liberal Studies Service and Leadership Celebration, June 2020
  - Liberal Studies Toast to the Core Class of 2021, May 2021
- School of Law (RG 22), May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU Law Convocation 2021, May-June 2021
  - NYU Law Graduation, May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU Law Honoring the Graduating Class of 2020, May 2020
  - NYU Law: A Virtual Celebration for the Graduating Class of 2020, January 2021
- NYU Long Island School of Medicine (RG 23.12), June 2022
  - NYU Long Island School of Medicine Student Commencement & Events, June 2022
- College of Dentistry (RG 25), June 2020-June 2022
  - NYU Dentistry Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, June 2020
  - NYU Dentistry Class of 2021 Virtual Graduation, May 2021
  - NYU Dentistry Graduation, June 2022-ongoing
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26), May 2020-ongoing
  - Celebrating NYU Steinhardt's Class of 2020, June 2020
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development 2021 Baccalaureate and Valedictory Ceremonies, June-July 2021
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development 2021 Doctoral Convocation, June-July 2021
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Afternoon Ceremony Live Stream 2024 Graduation, June 2024
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Baccalaureate Ceremony Live Stream, June 2023
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Departmental Awards, May 2021-ongoing
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Doctoral Convocation Live Stream, June 2023-ongoing
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Graduation, May 2020-ongoing
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Leadership and Service Awards, May 2021-ongoing
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Morning Ceremony Live Stream 2024 Graduation, June 2024
  - Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development Valedictory Celebration Live Stream, June 2023
- Stern School of Business, The Undergraduate College (RG 27), May 2020-June 2024
  - NYU Stern 2020 Virtual Celebrations FAQ, May 2020
  - NYU Stern Class of 2020 Graduation, December 2020
  - NYU Stern Class of 2020 Undergraduate Virtual Celebration, January 2021
  - NYU Stern Class of 2021 Undergraduate Celebration, June 2021
  - NYU Stern Class of 2021 Virtual Celebration Event Program, June 2021
  - NYU Stern Class of 2022 Ceremonies, June 2022
  - NYU Stern Class of 2023, June 2023
  - NYU Stern Class of 2024 Ceremonies, June 2024
  - NYU Stern Graduation Ceremonies Livestream, June-July 2023
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate Baccalaureate Video, July 2023
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate Celebration, June 2021
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate Class of 2020 Celebration, May-June 2020
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate Class of 2020 Celebration, December 2020
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate Class of 2021 Virtual Celebration, July 2021
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate College Class of 2020 Graduates, June 2020
  - NYU Stern Virtual Celebrations, May-June 2020
- Stern School of Business, The Graduate Division (RG 28), June 2020-August 2022
  - NYU Stern Class of 2021 Graduate Celebration, June 2021-August 2022
  - NYU Stern Executive Programs 2020 Virtual Celebration, December 2020
  - NYU Stern Graduate Celebration, June 2021
  - NYU Stern Graduate Class of 2020 Celebration, December 2020
  - NYU Stern Graduate Class of 2020 Celebration, June 2020
  - NYU Stern Graduate Class of 2020 Celebration Program, May-June 2020
  - NYU Stern Graduate Class of 2021 Virtual Celebration, July 2021
    Scope and Contents
    This web page includes video clips of the in-person convocation ceremony as well as tributes to the Classes of 2020 and 2021 from faculty and staff.
  - NYU Stern Graduate Convocation for the Class of 2020 and 2021 Recap, July 2022
  - NYU Stern Graduate Convocation for the Class of 2022 Recap, July 2022
  - NYU Stern Graduate Marching Order Commencement Website, May-December 2020
- School of Professional Studies (RG 32), May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU School of Professional Studies 2020 Graduate Virtual Celebration, May 2020
  - NYU School of Professional Studies 2020 Undergraduate Virtual Celebration, May 2020
  - NYU School of Professional Studies Graduates Graduation Ceremonies, May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU School of Professional Studies Virtual Convocation Celebration, May 2021
  - NYU School of Professional Studies Virtual Convocation Celebration, May 2021
- Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (RG 33), May 2020-ongoing
  - Highlights from the NYU Wagner Class of 2023 Convocation, June 2023
  - Highlights from the NYU Wagner Class of 2024 Convocation, June 2024
  - NYU Wagner Graduation, May 2020-ongoing
    Youtube video of the Wagner virtual commencement on May 21, 2020.
  - NYU Wagner Virtual Grad Celebration 2020, June 2020
- Silver School of Social Work (RG 34), June 2020-ongoing
  - Silver School of Social Work Celebrating the Class of 2020, June 2020
  - Silver School of Social Work Celebrating the Class of 2021, May 2021
  - Silver School of Social Work Celebrating the Class of 2022, June 2022
  - Silver School of Social Work Celebrating the Class of 2023, June 2023
  - Silver School of Social Work Celebrating the Class of 2024, June 2024
  - Silver School of Social Work Celebrating the Classes of 2020 and 2021, June 2022
  - Silver School of Social Work Class of 2020 Tribute Video, July 2022
  - Silver School of Social Work Class of 2023 Graduation, June 2023
  - Silver School of Social Work Graduation, June 2024
  - Silver School of Social Work Tribute to the NYU Silver Class of 2021, July 2022
- Tisch School of the Arts (RG 35), May 2020-ongoing
  - Tisch School of the Arts Graduation, May 2020-ongoing
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2020, May 2020
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2021, May-June 2021
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2023, June 2023
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2023: Billy Crudup, June 2023
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2023: Darius Adamson, June 2023
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2023: Dean Allyson Green, June 2023
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2023: President Andrew Hamilton, June 2023
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2024, June 2024
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute 2024 Photo Gallery, June 2024
  - Tisch School of the Arts Virtual Salute to Class of 2021, June 2021
- Gallatin Division (RG 36), May 2020-ongoing
  - Gallatin Class of 2024 Graduation Awardees, June 2024
  - Gallatin Graduation, July 2022
  - Gallatin Graduation 2021, May 2021
  - Gallatin Graduation Awards and Honors, June 2020-ongoing
  - Gallatin Graduation Ceremonies, May 2020-ongoing
  - Gallatin Homepage, May 2020-August 2022
- Tandon School of Engineering (RG 48), May 2020-July 2024
  - Tandon School of Engineering 166th Virtual Commencement, May 2021
  - Tandon School of Engineering 2020 Commencement Awards, May 2020
  - Tandon School of Engineering Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, January 2021
  - Tandon School of Engineering Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, May-December 2020
  - Tandon School of Engineering Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, May 2020
  - Tandon School of Engineering Class of 2020: Your Vision. Your Future, May 2020
  - Tandon School of Engineering Class of 2024 Commencement, June-July 2024
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement, June 2022-ongoing
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2020, May 2020
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2021, June 2021
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2023, June 2023
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2023, June 2023
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2023, June-July 2023
  - Tandon School of Engineering Commencement 2024, June 2024
  - Tandon School of Engineering Virtual Celebration, May 2020
  - Tandon School of Engineering Virtual Commencement, May 2021
- NYU Abu Dhabi (RG 49), May 2020-ongoing
  - Congratulations #NYUAD2020: Commencement Pre-Show, June 2020
  - Congratulations #NYUAD2020: Part 1, January 2021
  - Congratulations #NYUAD2020: Part 2, January 2021
  - NYU Abu Dhabi 2020 Commencement - Live Version, January 2021
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Class of 2020: A Tribute, June 2020
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Class of 2020: Global Tribute, June 2020
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Class of 2020: NYUAD's 10th Anniversary, June 2020
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Class of 2020: Travel Memories, January 2021
    This webpage provides information about the virtual celebrations for graduates of NYU Abu Dhabi.
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Class of 2024 Yearbook Submissions, June 2024
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement, May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement 2020 Magazine, June 2020
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement 2022 Order of Exercises, June 2021-June 2022
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement 2024
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Commencement 2024: Presentation of Candidates
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Dear Class of 2024
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Seventh Commencement Exercises Program, June 2020
  - NYU Abu Dhabi We Are Not Strangers, January 2021
  - Vice Chancellor Mariët Westermann Congratulates #NYUAD2020, January 2021
- NYU Shanghai (RG 50), May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU Shanghai 2021 Commencement, July 2021-ongoing
  - NYU Shanghai Class of 2024 Graduate Convocation, June 2024
  - NYU Shanghai Commencement, May 2020-ongoing
  - NYU Shanghai Commencement, June 2024
  - NYU Shanghai Commencement 2023 Livestream, June 2023
  - NYU Shanghai Eighth Commencement Exercises, June 2024
- Rory Meyers College of Nursing (RG 52), May 2020-ongoing
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing 2022 Graduation Ceremony, June 2022
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing 2022 Graduation Ceremony, July 2022
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing 2022 Pinning Ceremony, July 2022
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Class of 2020 Virtual Celebration, January 2021
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Graduation Site, June 2022-ongoing
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Program for 2020 Virtual Celebration for Graduating Students, June-December 2020
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Virtual Celebration, May 2020-ongoing
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Virtual Celebration for the Class of 2020, May 2020
- School of Global Public Health (RG 53), May 2020-ongoing
  - School of Global Public Health 2021 Graduation Celebration Video, June 2021
  - School of Global Public Health 2022 Graduation Ceremony, June 2022
  - School of Global Public Health 2022 Graduation Congratulatory Video, June 2022
  - School of Global Public Health 2023 Graduation Ceremony, June 2023
  - School of Global Public Health 2024 Graduation, June 2024
  - School of Global Public Health 2024 Graduation Ceremony at New York City Center, June 2024
  - School of Global Public Health Graduation Celebration, May 2020-ongoing
  - School of Global Public Health Graduation Celebration 2020, June 2020
  - School of Global Public Health Graduation Celebration 2020, January 2021
  - School of Global Public Health Graduation Ceremony, May 2021